<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What&#39;s New :: Hugo Relearn Theme</title>
    <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/index.html</link>
    <description>What&#39;s new in this version</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Version 5</title>
      <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/5/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/5/index.html</guid>
      <description>5.27.0 (2024-04-07) Hugo 0.121.0 0.121.0 This release requires a newer Hugo version. Change Change If the theme is configured to generate warnings or errors during build by setting image.errorlevel to either warning or error in your hugo.toml, it will now also generate output if a link fragment is not found in the target page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 4</title>
      <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/4/index.html</guid>
      <description>4.2.0 (2022-06-23) Breaking Breaking The second parameter for the include shortcode was switched in meaning and was renamed from showfirstheading to hidefirstheading. If you haven’t used this parameter in your shortcode, the default behavior hasn’t changed and you don’t need to change anything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 3</title>
      <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/3/index.html</guid>
      <description>3.4.0 (2022-04-03) Breaking Breaking If you had previously overwritten the custom-footer.html partial to add visual elements below the content of your page, you have to move this content to the new partial content-footer.html. custom-footer.html was never meant to contain HTML other than additional styles and JavaScript. New New If you prefer expandable/collapsible menu items, you can now set collapsibleMenu=true in your hugo.toml. This will add arrows to all menu items that contain sub menus. The menu will expand/collapse without navigation if you click on an arrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 2</title>
      <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/2/index.html</guid>
      <description>2.9.0 (2021-11-19) Breaking Breaking This release removes the themes implementation of ref/relref in favor for Hugo’s standard implementation. This is because of inconsistencies with the themes implementation. In advantage, your project becomes standard compliant and exchanging this theme in your project to some other theme will be effortless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1</title>
      <link>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mcshelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/introduction/releasenotes/1/index.html</guid>
      <description>1.2.0 (2021-07-26) New New Shortcode expand with new parameter to open on page load. 1.1.0 (2021-07-02) Breaking Breaking Mermaid diagrams can now be panned and zoomed. This isn’t configurable yet. New New Mermaid config options can be set in hugo.toml. 1.0.0 (2021-07-01) Hugo 0.65.0 0.65.0 The requirement for the Hugo version of this theme is the same as for the Learn theme version 2.5.0 on 2021-07-01. New New Initial fork of the Learn theme based on Learn 2.5.0 on 2021-07-01. This introduces no new features besides a global rename to Relearn and a new logo. For the reasons behind forking the Learn theme, see this comment in the Learn issues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>