<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on Hugo Relearn Theme</title>
    <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on Hugo Relearn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/migration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/migration/index.html</guid>
      <description>This document shows you what&amp;rsquo;s new in the latest release. For a detailed list of changes, see the history page.
Breaking A change that requires action by you after upgrading to assure the site is still functional.
Change A change in default behavior. This may requires action by you / may or may not be revertable by configuration.
New Marks new behavior you might find interesting or comes configurable.
5.9.0 (2022-12-23) Change The required folder name for the attachments shortcode was changed for leaf bundles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Requirements</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/requirements/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/requirements/index.html</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the simplicity of Hugo, this page is as empty as this theme needs requirements.
Just download latest version of Hugo binary for your OS (Windows, Linux, Mac) : it&amp;rsquo;s that simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following steps are here to help you initialize your new website. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know Hugo at all, we strongly suggest you learn more about it by following this great documentation for beginners.
Create your project Hugo provides a new command to create a new website.
hugo new site &amp;lt;new_project&amp;gt; Install the theme Install the Relearn theme by following this documentation using Hugo&amp;rsquo;s module system.
This theme&amp;rsquo;s repository is: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/configuration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/configuration/index.html</guid>
      <description>Global site parameters On top of Hugo global configuration, the Relearn theme lets you define the following parameters in your config.toml (here, values are default).
Note that some of these parameters are explained in details in other sections of this documentation.
[params] # This controls whether submenus will be expanded (true), or collapsed (false) in the # menu; if no setting is given, the first menu level is set to false, all others to true; # this can be overridden in the pages frontmatter alwaysopen = true # Prefix URL to edit current page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customization</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/customization/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/customization/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Relearn theme has been built to be as configurable as possible by defining multiple partials
In themes/hugo-theme-relearn/layouts/partials/, you will find all the partials defined for this theme. If you need to overwrite something, don&amp;rsquo;t change the code directly. Instead follow this page. You&amp;rsquo;d create a new partial in the layouts/partials folder of your local project. This partial will have the priority.
This theme defines the following partials :
header.html: the header of the page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stylesheet generator</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/generator/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/generator/index.html</guid>
      <description>This interactive tool may help you to generate your own color variant stylesheet.
To get started, first select a color variant from the variant switch that fits you best as a starting point.
The graph is interactive and reflect the current colors. You can click on any of the colored boxes to adjust the respective color. The graph and the page will update accordingly.
The arrowed lines reflects how colors are inherited thru different parts of the theme if the descendent isn&amp;rsquo;t overwritten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/history/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://McShelby.github.io/hugo-theme-relearn/basics/history/index.html</guid>
      <description>Changelog 5.9.4 (2023-01-23) Fixes [bug] variant: fix search icon and text color #437 5.9.3 (2023-01-22) Fixes [bug] nav: fix left/right navigation for horizontal scrolling #435 [bug] theme: allow pages on top level #434 Maintenance [task] build: switch to wildcard version of actions #428 5.9.2 (2022-12-30) Fixes [bug] search: apply dependency scripts for Hindi and Japanese #427 5.9.1 (2022-12-23) Enhancements [feature] theme: make external link target configurable #426 5.9.0 (2022-12-23) Enhancements [feature][change] theme: open external links in separate tab #419 [feature] theme: make it a Hugo module #417 Fixes [bug][change] attachments: fix incorrect links for defaultContentLanguageInSubdir=true #425 5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>